const STORE = [
  {
    question: 'What is the proper term for a group of kittens?',
    answers: ['Kindle', 'Kaboodle', 'Karat', 'Keel'],
    correct: 'Kindle'
  },
  {
    question: 'All cats are born with what color eyes?',
    answers: ['Blue', 'Green', 'White', 'Red'],
    correct: 'Blue'
  },
  {
    question: 'How many hours do cats sleep in a day?',
    answers: ['1-2', '3-6', '8-12', '12-16'],
    correct: '12-16'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the smallest breed of cat?',
    answers: ['Munchkin', 'Sphynx', 'Singapura','Tabby'],
    correct: 'Singapura'
  },
  {
    question: 'How many whiskers do cats have?',
    answers: ['10', '14', '18', '24'],
    correct: '24'
  },
  {
    question: 'What do you call it when a cat grooms other cats or a human?',
    answers: ['Affection', 'Nasty', 'Allogrooming', 'Bookmarking'],
    correct: 'Allogrooming'
  },
  {
    question: 'How many toes does a normal cat have?',
    answers: ['10','14','18','24'],
    correct: '18'
  },
  {
    question: 'Cats who have more than 18 toes are called what?',
    answers: ['Polydactyl', 'Freaks', 'Multi-beaned', 'Pawtiful'],
    correct: 'Polydactyl'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of these foods is toxic to cats?',
    answers: ['Chocolate','Grapes','Onions','All of These'],
    correct: 'All of These'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the most popular cat breed?',
    answers: ['Abyssinian', 'Siamese', 'Persian', 'Maine Coon'],
    correct: 'Persian'
  }
]